本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
总统阁下  我们找到了您的丈夫
Madam president, we have your husband,
可是他胸部中枪
But he sustained a gunshot wound to the chest.
我丈夫能挺过去吗
is my husband going to be okay?
这得等医生诊断后才知道
We're not going to know anything until the doctors see him.
既然您丈夫是杜巴库唯一的筹码
Since your husband was the only leverage that Dubaku had left,
现在可以肯定他会试图越境
It's safe to say that he's trying to leave the country now.
不管我们采取什么行动找到他
Whatever we're going to do to find him,
都得快马加鞭了
We're going to have to do it fast.
不惜一切代价
Whatever it takes,
一定要找到那个狗杂种
I want that son of a bitch found!
派人去找我女儿奥利维亚
Have someone find my daughter, Olivia,
把她带来见我
And bring her to me.
什么事那么重要
What is it that's so important
我妈非得在我谈生意时
For my mother to steal me away while I'm trying
-唤我出来  -你爸出事了
- To do business? - It's your father.
他中枪了
He's been shot.
天哪  我...
My, god, i...
你以为我是傻子吗  伯内特先生
Do you think I'm a fool, Mr. Burnett?
如果我在逃离这个国家的途中
If anything should happen to me
遭遇不测
On my way out of the country,
一份写满涉案人员的的黑名单
A data file with all the names and bank transactions
和银行交易的文档将被会送到司法部门
Of all those involved will be sent to the justice department.
你说过一旦杜巴库得偿所愿
You told me that once Dubaku served his purpose,
你就会把他干掉
You'd take him out.
我们为什么还要帮他
Why are we still helping him?
他保留了资料库  以揭发我们相要挟
He's threatening to expose us using a database he's kept
其中包括所有涉案人员的名字和帐户
With names and accounts of everyone involved.
有我的吗
Including mine?
还不知道档案在哪里
We don't know where the file is,
所以你最好祈祷他能逃过此劫
So you just better pray that he gets away.
求你了  玛丽卡
I'm begging you, Marika...
联邦调查员  不许动
FBI! don't move!
跪下  快
Get on your knees! now!
杜巴库在哪里
Where is Dubaku?
谁
Who?
别耍花样  埃克·杜巴库
Don't play games with me! Ike Dubaku!
你认识这个人吗
you know this man?
她正要去见他
She was going to meet him.
等车到这里  我们希望你
When the car arrives, we would like you
能跟着司机走  以便我们能跟踪你
To go with the driver, so that we could follow you
顺藤摸瓜找到杜巴库
Back to Dubaku.
你想让她和杜巴库会面吗
You want her to go to him and face him?
这是他人间蒸发前我们找到他的
It's the  only chance we have of finding him before he
-最后一线希望  -我愿意
- Disappears forever. - I'll do it.
一定要确保她安然无恙  听到了吗
You keep her safe, you hear me?
一定
We will.
你们距离目标车辆不到一英里
You're less than a mile behind the target car.
首府警局在我们周围设置了路障
I got Metro PDs trying to build a roadblock around us.
千万不能让他们跑了  杰克
We can't afford to lose them, Jack!
我承诺会保护她
I gave this woman my word we'd protect her.
下车  放慢动作
Get out of the vehicle, slowly!
-她是联邦调查员  -跪下
She's a federal agent! on your knees!
-她是联邦调查员  -趴在地上
She's a federal agent! on the ground!
联调局说服了你马子
Your girlfriend's been turned by the FBI.
如果她去见你
If you let her come to you,
你就很难开溜
You're risking your chances of escape.
我会打电话给司机  让他处置她
I'll call my driver, have him take care of her.
不  我亲自处理
No. I'll take care of her.
以下事件发生在下午五点到六点
The following takes place between 5:00 p.m.and 6:00 p.m.
翻译：非燕   lighthouse   Nil   校对：何何
■
后期：冰河   总监：何何
西恩
Sean,
-我想和你谈谈  -有要紧事吗
- I need to talk to you. - Is it important?
你说呢  你有没有签发
You tell me. did you issue
-对这辆车的逮捕令  -什么
- A federal warrant on this vehicle? - What?
我在4号服务器的备用分区上
I found a digital footprint
发现了一处历史记录
On server four's backup partition.
来源于你的工作台  我想知道
It originated from your station. I'd like to know
-究竟是怎么回事  -小声点
- What the hell is going on! - Keep your voice down.
你想让我们被抓起来吗
You want to get us caught?
我发出了逮捕令
I sent out the warrant,
拖住鲍尔和蕾妮
To sideline Bauer and Renee.
他们正围追杜巴库
They were closing in on Dubaku.
你说过杜巴库已经在越境的途中
I thought you said Dubaku's on his way out of the country?
没错  可是他马子正协助联调局
He is, but his girlfriend's talking to FBI.
他们利用她来追踪杜巴库
They used her to track him.
天哪
Oh, my god.
别担心  我会处理好的
Don't worry, I took care of it.
鲍尔和蕾妮已经被警方拘留
Bauer and Renee are in police custody.
等到他们被释放时
By the time they're released,
杜巴库早已远走高飞
Dubaku will be long gone.
确定吗
Are you sure?
确定
I'm positive.
你为什么不告诉我事态的发展呢
Why didn't you just tell me what was happening?
因为我就知道你会有过激反应
'cause I knew you'd react like this.
现在我只要你保持平静
The last thing I need right now is one of your meltdowns.
听着  是我拉你下水的
Now, listen, I got you into this,
我一定会让你全身而退
And I'm going to get you out of it,
可你绝不能方寸大乱
But not if you start panicking.
你得临阵不慌
You've got to keep it together.
我真被吓坏了  你知道吗
I'm just really scared, you know?
知道  我也是
I know. I am, too.
我只是比你更擅长瞒天过海
I'm just a little better at hiding it than you are.
一切都已安排得天衣无缝
I've got everything covered.
我在监听会议室
I ran a bounce-tap into the conference room
他们不会发现我在扩音器里装了窃听器
Speakerphone that they'll never find,
我可以窃听他们的谈话
And I can hear everything they're saying.
现在你就乖乖待在你的工作台
Now, sit at your station.
表现得一如往常就好了
Try and act normal.
我来处理鲍尔和蕾妮
Let me worry about Bauer and Renee.
好吗
Okay?
我们追踪的人
The man that we were tracking is responsible
是今天发生的恐怖袭击的主谋
For today's terrorist attack.
你不放了我们  他就会逃之夭夭
If you don't let us go, he's going to get away.
我的队长正在和你的上司打电话
Look, my captain's on the phone with your superior.
你们错了
You're making a mistake!
放我们走
You've got to let us go!
逮捕令一定是杜巴库手下卧底发的
That warrant had to be sent out by one of Dubaku's operatives.
-我知道  -他也会知道玛丽卡是我们一伙的
I know. then Dubaku knows that Marika is working with us.
他会杀人灭口  杰克
He will kill her, Jack.
我们不该利用她
We should not have used her like this.
我们别无选择  她是我们唯一的筹码
We didn't have a choice. she was our only asset.
她不是筹码  杰克  她是个大活人
She's not an asset, Jack. she's a human being.
上校
Colonel.
联调局还在找我们  先生
The FBI is still looking for us, sir.
我会速战速决  在原地待命
I'll do this quickly. wait there for me.
塞缪尔
Samuel.
怎么了
What? what is it?
亲爱的  怎么了
Sweetheart, what's wrong?
把手机给我
Give me your cell phone.
我的手机吗
My cell phone?
我知道你一直在和联调局联系
I know you've been talking to the FBI.
你一直为他们工作  玛丽卡
You've been working for them, Marika.
你胡言乱语什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你到底在干什么
What? what are you doing?
不
No!
我那么相信你
I trusted you!
你怎么可以这么对我
How could you do this to me?!
联调局告诉了我你的真面目
The FBI told me who you really are.
还有你犯下的累累罪行
About the terrible things you've done.
-你竟然相信了他们  -他们给我看了证据
- And you believed them? - They showed me proof!
他们给你看的是我敌人捏造的伪证
They showed you lies created by my enemies!
你不了解我
You don't know me.
也不了解我的祖国
And you don't know my country.
我给桑加拉带来了和平
I brought peace to Sangala.
别
No. shh, shh!
别害怕
Don't be afraid, huh?
只是
It's just...
当我得知你背叛了我时
When I heard what you had done,
那一刻  就像是
It was like you had
你将匕首刺穿了我的心脏
Driven a dagger through my heart.
我是个宽宏大量的男人  玛丽卡
I'm a forgiving man, Marika.
我仍旧希望你跟我远走高飞
I still want you to come with me.
我想让你过上我承诺过的好日子
I want to give you the life that I promised.
我不能跟你走
I can't go with you.
我不知道你究竟是谁
I don't know who you are.
你知道
You do.
你知道  如果你的目光不再停留在恐惧感上
You do. if you look past your fear,
你会明白我还是原来那个
You'll see that I am still the man that you
和你相爱的人
Fell in love with.
我不会撇下你一个人走  玛丽卡
I won't leave without you, Marika.
好吧
All right.
我不会让你失望的
You won't be disappointed.
来
Come.
联调局证实了你说的话
Your story was verified by FBI.
抱歉误解了你
I'm sorry about the misunderstanding.
联调局找到玛丽卡·道诺索了吗
Did FBI find Marika Donoso?
不清楚  你可以自己问他们
I don't know. you can ask them yourself.
莫斯探员想和你通话
Agent Moss wants to talk to you.
拉里  他们在哪里  玛丽卡在哪里
Larry, where are they? where's Marika?
-她的手机信号中断了  -什么意思
- We lost her cell phone signal. - What do you mean?
-出了什么事  -不知道
- What happened? - I don't know.
三分钟前突然中断了信号
Just went dead about three minutes ago.
-在哪里  -一条小巷里
- Where? - In an alley
在N大街和第十大街东北角
On the northeast corner of N and 10th Street.
我正在查看电子眼的监控录像
I'm looking through traffic cams now.
好  我们这就出发  随时待命
All right, we're going to come. standby.
玛丽卡的信号中断了
They lost Marika's signal.
-找到了  -杰克
- That's it. there. - Jack?
我们确认了车辆的型号  深灰色
We got a make on the car. it's a dark gray
是辆大切诺基吉普车  大约两分钟前
Jeep Grand Cherokee, turned south on 11th Street
-在第十一大街向南转向  -收到
- About two minutes ago. - Copy that.
-准备赶去拦截  -看见玛丽卡了吗
- Moving to intercept. - Did you see Marika?
看到了  她和杜巴库一起上的车
Yes. she got in the car with Dubaku.
-克罗伊  继续监控电子眼  -我在监控
- Chloe, stay on those traffic cams. - I'm on it.
我们离机场十分钟车程
We're ten minutes from the airfield.
飞机准备好了吗
Is my plane ready?
已经加完油等候起飞了
Fueled and waiting.
你把问题解决了吗
Did you take care of the problem?
她已经改变了心意
She's had a change of heart.
和我一起走
She's coming with me.
上校  她和联调局合作
Colonel, she was working with the FBI.
你差点因为她而被捕
You were almost arrested because of her.
你不用管她
She's not your concern.
只要把我弄出国就好
You just worry about getting me out of the country.
你和谁通话
Who was that?
一个政府官员
It was a government official.
一直为我效力
He's been working for me.
是个腐败分子
A very corrupt man.
我可不愿再和这种败类为伍了
I look forward to no longer dealing with people like him.
我想和我真正在乎的人厮守终生
I want to spend time with people I really care about.
他们还在第十一大街
they're still on 11th.
刚过十字路口到纽约大街
They just crossed over to New York Avenue.
收到
Copy that.
快点啊
Come on!
-杰克  他们左拐了  -抓稳了
- Jack, they're turning left. - Hold on.
联调局  快跑  快
FBI. go! go!
抓稳
Hold on!
爬上车顶  看看能否还能看到他们
Get on top of the car! see if you can maintain a visual.
玛丽卡
Ow! Marika!
Marika!
杰克  他们翻车了
Jack, they crashed!
走
Go!
回到车里
Get back in your car!
拉里  杜巴库的车出了车祸
Larry, Dubaku's vehicle's been involved in an accident.
我们需要救护车  快
We need an ambulance, now!
收到
Copy.
闪开
Back away!
跪下
Stay on your knees!
趴在地上  快
Get on the ground, now!
快
Now!
找到杜巴库了
I got Dubaku.
沃克探员  车子着火了
Agent Walker, the car is on fire.
快离开
Get out of there!
我给过她承诺  你不帮我的话
I gave her my word, so back off
就给我退后
Or help me.
她的腿被压住了
it's her leg-- it's pinned.
抓住
Hold on.
拉  拉
Pull... pull!
杰克
Jack.
走  快走
Go! Go!
没事吧
You all right?
快
come on.
拉里  救护车在哪里
Larry, where is my ambulance?
杜巴库严重受伤
Dubaku's badly injured.
他失去了知觉
He's unconscious.
我现在就要救护车
I need that ambulance now.
快到了  杰克
They're on their way, Jack.
我们会在一小时内解放桑加拉首府
We'll have the capitol of Sangala secured within the hour.
他很惊讶我军 仅遇到如此微薄的抵抗
He's surprised how little resistance Our troops have encountered.
您应该感到高兴  我们解放了
And you'll be happy to know we have liberated
卡桑加省的难民营
The refugee camp in Kasanga province.
2000名平民逃离了朱玛军队的魔掌
2,000 civilians are safe from Juma's forces.
总统阁下
Madam president?
抱歉  伊桑
I'm sorry, Ethan.
天哪  卡桑加省
Oh, my god, Kasanga province.
真是个好消息
That's... that's very good news.
可能我们应该
Uh, maybe we should
另找时间谈这些
Finish this another time.
我能为您效劳吗
Can I get you anything,
总统阁下
Madam president?
不用  谢谢
No, thank you.
想说说心里话吗
Would you like to talk about it?
亨利弄成这样都是我的错  伊桑
What happened to Henry was my fault, Ethan.
他一直不相信我们儿子是自杀
He never believed our son committed suicide.
他没错
He was right.
而我却置若罔闻
And I didn't listen to him.
如果我当时相信他
And if I had, we wouldn't
就不会是现在这个局面了
Be here right now.
亨利就不用冒死调查真相
Henry wouldn't be fighting for his life,
那样我们早就揭穿了阴谋
And we might have exposed this conspiracy.
整个政府也不会陷入瘫痪
Our government wouldn't be paralyzed.
我也没相信亨利
I didn't believe Henry, either.
谁都没信他
No one did.
但是我是他妻子
But I'm his wife.
他应当得到我的信任
He deserved my trust.
总统阁下
Madam president?
抱歉打扰了
I'm sorry to interrupt.
没关系  比尔
It's all right, Bill.
请讲吧
Go ahead.
我跟联调局的拉里·莫斯通过电话
I just spoke to Larry Moss at FBI.
我们抓到杜巴库了
We captured Dubaku.
追击的时候  发生了车祸
He was seriously injured in a car crash
-杜巴库伤得不轻  -有多严重
During the pursuit. how bad?
很危急  已经失去知觉了
Critical, nonresponsive.
杰克和沃克探员跟他在一起
Jack Bauer and agent Walker are with him.
杜巴库一恢复意识
They'll be there to question him
他们就会审问他
Should he regain consciousness.
那么你就是说  如果杜巴库死了
So, you're saying that if Dubaku dies, our chances
我们揭穿这个阴谋的机会也就成了泡影
Of uncovering this conspiracy die with him.
他很有可能是唯一一个
He could be the only one who knows
知道政府里所有腐败人员名单的人
The names of everyone in the government
是的没错
He's corrupted-- yes.
总统阁下
Madam president,
鉴于当前形势
Given this latest news, I don't think
我认为您在这是不安全的
It's safe for you to remain here.
强烈建议您回到白宫去
I strongly urge you to return to the White House.
我要跟我丈夫在一起
I'd prefer to stay with my husband.
您待在这里太显眼了
You're too exposed.
我不能有效地保护您
I can't effectively protect you.
在白宫里就会更安全了吗
Am I any safer at the White House?
我的政府
My administration
已经被彻底腐化了  比尔
Has been corrupted, Bill,
而你却告诉我  我们唯一的线索也快断了
And now you're telling me we're about to lose our only lead.
总统阁下  我保证在白宫里
Madam president, I assure you I've taken
会采取一切预防措施护驾
Every precaution to secure the White House.
现在那是最安全的地方
It's the safest place for you to be right now.
亨利的手术还得几个小时
Henry will be in surgery for several hours,
总统阁下
Madam president.
在这我们也是干着急
There's nothing more we can do here.
但是在总统办公室
You are needed
那里需要您
In the Oval Office.
好吧
All right.
我叫人把车发动着
I'll have the cars brought around.
同时让护送您女儿的车队改道去白宫
I'll also redirect your daughter's escorts to the White House.
谢谢你  比尔
Thank you, Bill.
下一步怎么办  伊桑
What are we going to do, Ethan?
如果我们都不知道谁值得信任
How can we possibly run this government
我们怎么才能让政府运作起来呢
When we don't know who we can trust?
我们只能祈祷杰克·鲍尔
We'll just have to pray Jack Bauer
能从杜马库那弄到那些名单
Can get those names from Dubaku.
-他情况稳定了吗  -是的  先生
- You got him stabilized?  - yes, sir.
-现在送他去医院  -把他弄醒
- We're transporting him right now.  - bring him around.
-我要和他讲话  -先生  他现在
- I need to talk to him.  - sir, he's in no condition
-不能讲话  -他掌握重要情报
- To speak right now.  - this man has information vital
关系到国家安全  把他弄醒
To national security-- bring him around now.
快
Now!
一毫克肾上腺素
One milligram epinephrine.
我知道你听得见  你现在已被逮捕
I know you can hear me. you're in federal custody.
这些医生在抢救你
These paramedics are trying to save your life.
如果你不想死
You want them to continue, you're gonna
就统统交代出
Tell me what I want to know. I want the names of everyone
你那些潜伏在政府里的同党
in the United States Government that you've been working with.
别装了
Come on.
你我都知道
You and I both know the game.
游戏已经结束了
It's over for you now.
没必要再去保护他们
There's no sense in trying to protect them.
你我都是军人
You and I, we're both soldiers.
我知道你不怕死
I know you don't care about your own life,
但你还有家庭
But you got a family.
你儿子还在桑加拉
I know where your son is in Sangala.
我知道他在哪里
I know where he lives, and I swear to you,
我发誓我会找到他  折磨他
I will track him down, and I will make him suffer,
而且会告诉他这一切
And I will make sure that he knows
都是他父亲的过错
His father was responsible.
除非你给我那些人的名字
All you got to do to make me stop is give me the names.
告诉我名字
Just give me the names.
别碰我的家人
Don't hurt my family.
我有一份名单
I have a list... list.
在哪里
Where is the list?
-他的血压在下降  -给我名单
- His BP's spiking.  - give me the list.
名单在哪里
Where is the list?!
他的心跳停止了
He's going into cardiac arrest.
-快救活他  -电击板
- Bring him back!  - get the paddles.
从200焦开始
Start at 200 joules.
让开
clear.
-没有心跳  -有点问题
- No response--  - there's a glitch.
再来一次
Once more.
让开
Clear.
又出现了
There it is again.
有电磁干扰
Electronic interference.
可能是这个  像是金属盘之类的东西
This could be it-- feels like a metal plate or something.
好了
all right.
增大到300焦
Amping up to 300.
-让开  -盘在哪里
- Clear.  - where's the plate?
行了
All right.
他情况稳定了  送他上车
He's stabilized-- let's get him boarded.
-盘在哪里   -在肋骨下方
- Where's the plate?  - it's below his rib cage.
给他开刀
Open him up.
先生  我们没时间了
Sir, we don't have time.
-请你别管了  -快给他开刀
- I have to ask you to step aside.  - You open him up now.
开吧
Do it.
先生  不送他去医院
Sir, this man will die
这个人就会死掉
If we don't get him to the hospital.
把他送走
Get him out of here.
让莫斯探员接电话
Patch me through to agent Moss.
我是莫斯
This is Moss.
拉里  我是杰克
Larry, it's Jack.
请讲  杰克
Go ahead, Jack.
我发现了植入在杜巴库
I found some kind of digital
皮肤下的电子存储器
Storage device implanted under Dubaku's skin.
-是什么  -为了保护他的家庭
- What is it?  - in an effort to protect his family,
他说会给我
He said he would provide me
他在政府里的同党名单
With a list of all of his U.S. Government contacts.
他说在他身上  就在体内
He said it was on him; he meant, in him.
拉里  这是他的护身符
Larry, this is his insurance policy.
-我肯定  -杰克  我们要尽快弄到名单
- I'm sure of it. - Jack, we need that data as soon as possible.
-能上传到联调局吗  -不行
- Can you upload the files to FBI? - I don't think so.
我从没见过这种东西
I've never seen anything like it.
等下
Hold on one second.
警官
Officer.
我是杰克·鲍尔
My name is Jack Bauer.
我是联调局的人
I'm working with the FBI.
请把这东西送到地区总部去
I need you to get this device to regional headquarters.
交给拉里·莫斯探员
I want you to give it to an agent Larry Moss.
只能亲手交给他本人
You put this in his hands, his hands only.
明白了吗  -是  先生
- You understand?  - yes, sir.
去吧
Do it.
拉里  有架直升机正赶往你那里
Larry, you got a chopper coming your way.
5分钟后你就可以拿到它
You should have the drive in five minutes.
我们得和杜巴库在一起
We're gonna stay with Dubaku.
有消息就通知我们
Get back to us as soon as you got anything.
好的
Copy that.
西恩
Sean.
怎么了
What is it?
出了什么事
What's wrong?
听我说  别太激动
Just listen to me, and try not to overreact.
出了点状况
Okay, we have a situation,
但我觉得我可以解决
But I think I have a way to handle it.
什么状况  你说一切都在你掌控中
What situation? you told me you had everything under control.
是的
I do...
-可他们弄到了杜巴库的名单   -什么
- But they have Dubaku's database.  - what?
西恩  我们的名字都在上面
Sean, our names are on that list.
你说过你会处理好这件事
You told me that you were taking care
可现在又说
Of this, and now you're telling me
-他们有我们的名字  -不  还没到那步
- That they have our names?  - no, they don't
现在的计划是
Have our names yet, so here's the plan.
西恩  我们得离开这里
Sean, we have to get out of here.
马上走
We have to get out of here right now!
我不想进监狱
I'm not going to jail, Sean!
-你听到没有  -谁都不会进监狱
- Do you hear me?  - nobody's going to jail.
-我保证  -少来这套
- I promise.  - I'm sick of your promises.
你上次不是保证过
You promised me that this
一切都搞定了吗
Is all taken care of.
你还保证说要和你老婆离婚
You promised me you're leaving your wife.
你说过那么多承诺
You make all these promises,
-没兑现过一个  -住口
- But you never keep any of them!  - stop talking,
听我说  我说过我自有办法
And just listen to me-- now, I told you I have a way
但我需要你帮忙  懂吗
Out of this, but I need your help, do you understand that?
听我说  好吗
Now, listen... okay?
奥布赖恩把文件下载后
As soon as O'Brian downloads those files,
我们就搞垮整个系统
We're gonna crash the entire system,
搞垮这层楼的每台服务器
Every single server on this floor.
天方夜谭
That's crazy.
不是天方夜谭
No, it's not crazy.
我们去主机房
We're gonna go up to the mainframe room...
开始系统格式化
Initiate a system-wide reformat.
清除一切信息
We'll wipe everything clean,
让他们没法阻止这一切
And they won't be able to stop it.
我们得绕过很多安全协议
We're gonna have to bypass a lot of safety protocols, okay?
但没有人
But nobody's better at dealing
比你更在行
With those servers than you are.
是吧
Isn't that true?
我需要你帮忙
I need your help.
没有你不行
I can't do this without you.
艾丽卡
Erika?
好的
Okay.
我们得把...
We're gonna have to...
主机都联一起
Tie the main servers together.
我需要一块AVI主板
I need an AVI motherboard,
但你得重新配置下
But you're gonna have to reconfigure it
让它进行宏上链
For a macro uplink.
好  我们得快点
Okay, and we have to hurry.
那块磁盘很快就会送到这了
The drive is gonna be here any minute.
你去主机房开始行动
Go up to the mainframe room and get started.
我先去弄主板
I'm gonna prep the motherboard.
再去那里找你
I'll meet you up there.
好
Okay.
一切会好起来的
We're gonna be fine.
我爱你
I love you.
我也是
I love you, too.
好  走吧
Okay, let's go. okay.
这些是玛丽卡·道诺索的私人物品
These are Marika Donoso's personal effects.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的
Copy that.
保持联系
Get back to me.
是拉里
That was Larry.
他们得到了磁盘
they got the drive
克罗伊在破解中
Chloe's gonna be working on them.
几分钟后就会有结果
They should have something in the next few minutes.
你就只关心这件事
That's all that matters,
对吗  杰克
Right, Jack?
我也不想看到
I don't like what happened to Marika
玛丽卡有什么不测
Any more than you do.
我们已经尽力了
We did what was necessary.
你得想开点
You better figure out a way to live with it.
怎么想开  装作没发生过吗
How, Jack? Pretend that it never happened?
你就那么无动于衷吗
Is it that easy for you?
克罗伊一有消息
I'll let you know when
我会通知你
Chloe's got something.
磁盘在这里
Here it is.
这是PX-1-7磁盘
This is a PX-1-7 drive.
有自动擦除功能
It's got an auto-erase function.
我们只能下载一次
We've only got one download.
[检查载入的新数据中  检测到西格玛12加密模式]
Checking new data import. Encryption Sigma 12 dectected.
你去了哪里
Where have you been?
比我预计的时间长了些
Just took a little longer than I thought.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
查看监控录像  得盯着拉里和奥布赖恩
Checking surveillance. Got to keep an eye on Larry and O'Brian.
一旦我们下手
Once we do this, they're gonna
他们很快就会知道有人在这里捣鬼
Realize someone's up here in a few seconds.
我们得为自己想好退路
We'll have to make a clean exit.
还要花多久
How much longer is this going to take?
我刚绕过安全协议
I just have to bypass safety protocols.
一旦通过验证
Once they're down,
我就开始直接格式化
I'll start the reformat.
说
Go ahead.
杜巴库还没到机场
Dubaku hasn't arrived at the airfield,
他没接电话
And he's not answering his cell phone.
-出了什么事了  -他被联调局抓到了
- What's going on?  - FBI got him.
什么
What?!
这件事你知道多久了
How long have you known about this?
他们不会从他那得到任何情报
They're not going to get anything out of him.
他在医院处于昏迷状态
He's unconscious in the hospital.
他们在追捕中出了车祸
There was a crash during a chase.
听着  联调局弄到了
Listen, the FBI recovered that database
你说过的那些名单
You told me about, the list of names.
我正在删除它
I'm in the process of deleting it.
不能留下蛛丝马迹
I'm going to erase every trace of it.
不用我说你也知道失败的后果
I don't have to tell you what will happen if they get that list.
不会的  名单的事由我来搞定
They won't. I'm gonna take care of the database.
你得搞定杜巴库
You need to take care of Dubaku.
-别操心他  你得确保  -可恶
- Don't worry about him. you just make sure...  - damn it!
我得挂了
I got to go.
出什么事了
What's wrong?
-这样不行  -怎么不行了
- It-it isn't working. - what do you mean, it isn't working?
指令输进去了
All the inputs are active,
服务器也联网了  但就是不能格式化
The servers are aligned, but the reformat won't start.
岂有此理
It doesn't make any sense.
好好想想  艾丽卡
Okay, well, just-just think it through, Erika.
-你行的  -你安静点行吗
- Right? you can do this.  - Would you just shut up?
好吗
Okay?
行
Okay.
一定是三号服务器的问题
Has to be server three.
三号服务器上周
All right, server three was upgraded
升级过
Last week.
也就是说他们把
Which means they restored
磁盘分区恢复到了系统默认状态
The partitions to the system default settings.
我怎么会这么蠢
How could I be so stupid?
只要重新设置下参数就行
I just have to configure the parameters.
好了
Okay.
好了吗  这样就行了吗
Okay? is that it?
是的
I think so.
程序在运行中
Program's running.
出什么事了
What? What's happening? What's going on?
-硬盘正被格式化  -什么
- The hard drive's reformatting.  - what?
文件正被删除中
The files are being erased.
信息全部丢失
We're losing everything.
让它停下来
Well, make it stop.
-我没权限  -卸载PX-1-7磁盘
- I don't have the access.  - Get the PX-1-7 out.
太晚了  数据已被擦除
It's too late. It's erased.
这是人为的  不是系统故障
This is deliberate. it's not a glitch.
有人想搞垮系统
Someone's trying to crash the system.
主机房在哪里
Where's your mainframe room?
跟我来
Come on.
他们过来了
Here they come.
我们得离开这里
We got to get out of here.
-快完了  -艾丽卡
Almost there. Erika...
-完成了  -你确定吗
- It's done.  - Are you sure?
是的  还要几分钟才能完成格式化
Yeah. it'll take a few minutes for the reformat to be complete,
但已经没法阻止了
But there's no stopping it.
好的  宝贝
Oh, baby.
我就知道你行
I knew you could do it.
我们没事了吧
Yeah. we gonna be okay?
没事了
We're gonna be fine.
对不起
Sorry.
趴下
Get on the floor!
不是我干的
It wasn't me!
趴下
Get on the floor!
拉里  不是我干的
Larry, it wasn't me.
克罗伊
Chloe!
拉里  我跟她来到这里
Larry, I followed her up here.
是她想把系统搞崩溃
She was trying to crash the system.
她还开枪打我
She shot me!
我去夺枪  结果枪走火了
I went for the weapon, and it went off.
警卫  我是莫斯探员
Security, this is agent Moss.
派一队人过来封锁主机房
I need a team to lock down the mainframe room.
派个医生过来  克罗伊  你能恢复文件吗
And get a medic up here! Chloe, can you recover the files?
不知道
I don't know yet.
什么文件  出了什么事
What files?! what the hell is happening?!
你倒说说到底出了什么事  西恩
You tell me what the hell is happening, Sean!
你不让我参加行动  所以我就自己调查了
You were shutting me out, Larry, so I looked around on my own.
我发现艾丽卡在重新设定摄像头
I found out that Erika was rerouting the sub-cam channel!
她想干什么
What the hell was she doing?
她还对两个嫌犯乘坐的车发了通缉令
She sent out a-a warrant on a vehicle with two suspects.
我觉得不太对劲
I knew something was wrong.
这不是她的份内事
That's not part of her job.
我问过她  但她矢口否认
I asked her about it, and she tried to deny it.
她表现得很奇怪
She was acting very strangely.
你为什么不告发她
Why didn't you say anything?
我不清楚状况
I don't know what the hell it meant,
所以我侵入了她的硬盘
So I hacked into her hard drive,
发现了主服务器的结构图
And I found schematics for the main server.
安全协议的
Bypass codes
绕行指令
For the safety protocols.
我跟过来  看她究竟葫芦里卖的什么药
I followed her up here to see what she was up to.
我刚发现她要
The second I realized she was trying to crash
搞垮系统  就冲上去阻止她
The system, i-i confronted her.
她就开枪了
She shot me.
我去夺枪
I went for the gun.
拉里  我没想杀她
Larry, I didn't mean to kill her.
别动  别动
Halt! halt!
拉里  太晚了  系统已经完了
Larry, it's too late. the system's fried.
杜巴库的文件丢失了
Dubaku's files are gone.
你确定吗  不能再恢复了吗
Are you sure? can you recover anything?
服务器被删得一干二净  她得手了
The server's wiped clean. she got everything.
只有这些吗
Is this everything you got?
还不止
No, it's not.
我没时间打印出
I didn't have time to print out every single
艾丽卡机器上的所有消息
Message that came through Erika's workstation.
这只是她过去三天的活动
That's everything she was doing for the past three days.
听着  拉里
look, Larry,
我告诉过你事情的经过
I told you what happened.
我觉得你应该给我个解释
I feel like you owe me an explanation.
这里到底出了什么事
What the hell is going on here?
政府里有人已被杜巴库收买
The government's been compromised by Dubaku.
联调局  特勤局
FBI, Secret Service.
天晓得还有谁
God knows who else.
所以我让克罗伊参与行动  而不是你
That's why I shut you out, brought in Chloe O'Brian.
我们正在破译一份文件
We were in the middle of decrypting a file
上面有为杜巴库卖命的人名单
That had the names of everyone on Dubaku's payroll.
艾丽卡格式化服务器时连名单一起删除了
Erika erased it when she wiped the server.
那是我们唯一的线索
That was our only lead.
你早该告诉我这些的
You should have told me about this.
你早该相信我
You should have trusted me.
西恩  我当时不知道该信谁
Sean, I didn't know who to trust.
你没事吧  胳膊怎么样
You all right? how's your arm?
很疼  但是我能挺得住
It hurts like hell. it's fine.
你稍作调整后  我们需要你帮忙
Oh. when you're up for it, I'm gonna need you
写份笔录
To write a statement.
好的
Okay.
你得守口如瓶
And keep your mouth shut.
局里还有谁为杜巴库工作
We don't know who else in this building
我们还不清楚  喂
Might be working for Dubaku. yeah.
拉里  别问我怎么弄的  但我竟成功了
Larry, don't ask me how, but I did it.
你成功什么了
You did what?
我修复了杜巴库的文档
I recovered Dubaku's files.
什么
What?
遇到敏感数据时
I was running a mirror file on an outside server.
我总会在一个外部服务器上
I always do that when I'm dealing
启动一个镜像文件
With sensitive materials.
艾丽卡的参数设置精密很难破译出来
Erika's parameters were too narrow to catch it.
需要多长时间破译
How soon can you have it decrypted?
已经破译好了  其实一直在破译中
It's decrypted. it's been decrypting this entire time.
杜巴库 记录了所有人为他效力的证据
Dubaku kept Detailed evidence on everyone.
电话记录  酬金记录  都在呢
Phone logs, financial records-- it's all here.
你马上对照下联调局的员工表
Listen, I'm gonna need you to cross-check with FBI personnel.
西恩说艾丽卡是独自为杜巴库卖命
Sean said Erika was working by herself,
但是我不能完全确认
But I got to be 100% sure.
好  等一下
Okay. hold on.
好的
Yeah.
克洛伊修复了那些文件
Chloe recovered the files.
那太好了
That's great.
我该去做笔录了
I should get to that statement.
好
Yeah.
西恩
Sean?
等你做完笔录
When you're done there,
就下楼去见韦伯医生
I want you to go downstairs and see Dr. Weber.
你开枪击中了同事
You shot a fellow agent.
你得跟心理医生谈谈
You're gonna want to talk to somebody.
好的  长官
Yes, sir.
知道服务器 到底怎么了吗
Hey, do you have any idea What's going on with the servers?
不清楚
Not a clue.
整个系统都崩溃了
The whole system's down.
我想进主机房 保安不让进
I tried to get into the mainframe room, And security has got it locked off.
去问拉里吧  詹尼斯
Ask Larry about it, Janis.
你去哪
Where are you going?
我有任务在身
I got to run an errand.
现在吗
Now?
希林格探员  别动
Agent Hillinger. Dont't move.
好吧  好吧
All right, all right.
慢着
Hold off.
马上给我交代
You better start talking to me right now!
我要找律师
I'd like to speak with my attorney.
把他给我关到审讯室去
Put him in holding.
给我接白宫的比尔·布坎南
Get me Bill Buchanan at the White House.
我妹妹呢
Where is my sister?
玛丽卡呢
Where's Marika?
出了场车祸
There was an accident.
出什么事了
What happened?
玛丽卡死了
Marika didn't make it.
你  你什么意思
What-what do you mean?
她出了交通事故
There was a crash.
是在追捕过程中
Uh, it happened during the pursuit.
玛丽卡意外身亡
Marika was killed.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你说过要保护她的
You said that you'd protect her.
你说她会没事的
You said she'd be okay.
没有玛丽卡的帮助  我们就抓不到杜巴库
We wouldn't have caught Dubaku without Marika's help.
她很勇敢  真的很勇敢  罗莎
She was very, very brave, Rosa.
这是什么
What is this?
给我这个  就没事了吗
This is supposed to make everything okay?
玛丽卡是我的全部
Marika was all I had!
我把她的命交给你  你就这么让她死了
I trusted you with her life, and you let her die?!
真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
别碰我
Don't touch me!
你害死了我妹
You killed my sister!
你根本不在乎自己的行事手段
You didn't care how you did it
也不在乎谁会受到伤害
or who got hurt!
沃克探员
Agent Walker?
失陪一下
Excuse me.
我刚跟拉里通了电话
I just got off the phone with Larry.
杜巴库没撒谎
Dubaku wasn't lying.
硬盘上存着所有政府内
On the drive was a list
为他卖命的人的名单
Of everyone he was working with in the government.
已经准备好抓捕那些人了
They're getting ready to make arrests.
都结束了
It's over.
罗莎还在纠结
It's not over for Rosa.
玛丽卡的死  是个悲剧
What happened to Marika was a tragedy.
但是我不会站在这告诉你
But I'm not going to stand here
我们做错了  因为我们没有错
And tell you what we did was wrong, because we weren't.
她做出了自己的抉择  一个勇敢的抉择
She made a choice, a brave one,
她参与了行动  并且她成功了
To get involved, but she made it.
天哪  听听你都在说些什么  杰克
God, listen to yourself, Jack.
你一点人性都没有
You don't even sound human.
你就一点感觉也没有吗
Don't you feel anything?
我们是职责所在
We had a job to do!
我们的职责就是
To protect the hundreds if not
保护成千上万的无辜生命
Thousands of innocent lives
如果我们不那样做  一旦恐怖袭击发生了
That would not have had a choice
那些人  还有的选吗
If we let a terrorist attack take place.
我们没有做错
What we did wasn't wrong.
我们这样做  很有必要
It was necessary.
我看过你的档案
I read your file.
你老婆被杀的时候  你会心痛吗
When your wife was killed, did you feel that
还是只是告诉你自己  这也是必要的
Or did you just tell yourself that that was necessary?
你要我怎么样呢
What do you want from me?
你到底要我怎么做
What do you want from me?!
我只是想知道  你现在也感到悲痛
I just want to know that you feel something!
就像我一样  痛彻心扉
I want to know that you feel the same kind of pain that I do!
你能感觉到吗
Do you feel that?!
没事了
It's all right.
你会没事的
You're going to be all right.
只是需要点时间
It's going to take a while.
你最终会学会忍受这种痛苦的
But you will learn to live with it.
如果我不想学会忍受呢
What if I don't want to learn to live with it?
那就放弃吧
Then quit.
还有
And by the way,
你在车边救人时表演的绝技
That stunt you pulled by the car...
下次再拿枪指着我时
...you ever pull your weapon on me again,
你最好真想一枪打死我
You better intend to use it.
我真想
I did.
奥利维亚
Olivia.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我爸爸怎么样了
How's dad?
他还在做手术
He's still in surgery.
我们还在等消息
We're waiting for word.
他会转危为安吧
Is he going to be all right?
他伤得很重
He was seriously injured.
子弹
The bullet
穿透了他的肺部
Went through his lung.
利维
Livy.
医生们
The doctors are doing
在全力抢救
Everything they can.
谁干的
Who did this?
一言难尽啊
It's complicated.
我要知道  是谁向我爸爸开的枪
I want to know who shot my father!
你爸爸发现了
Your father found out about a conspiracy
政府内部的一个阴谋
Inside the government.
于是那些幕后黑手想杀他灭口
The people behind it tried to kill him.
是些什么人
Who are these people?
我们目前仍在调查中
We're trying to find out right now.
我只能告诉你这么多了
That's all I can tell you.
好吧  我要去医院
Okay, I want to go to the hospital.
他醒过来的时候
I want to be there
-我要他看见我  -不能去
When he wakes up. I can't let you do that.
拿枪打你爸爸的人仍然逍遥法外
The people who shot your father are still out there.
我不管  我要见爸爸
I don't care, I want to see dad!
不许犟嘴
This is not a debate.
我不能让你再出什么事了
I'm not going to risk anything happening to you.
你在白宫里老实待着
You're staying in the White House,
就这样吧
And that's the end of it.
总统阁下  比尔·布坎南来见您了
Madam president, Bill Buchanan is here to see you.
我马上出来
I'll be right out.
我们还有很多事要谈  奥利维亚
There's a lot we need to talk about, Olivia.
好多事情  不能再漠视下去了
We've been ignoring things for far too long.
爸爸中了枪  你才想起来跟我谈
It took dad getting shot for you to finally want to talk?
我们别再无休止地争吵下去了
Let's not go down this path.
真的不该再吵了
Not again.
也不该在今天吵
Not today.
待会儿我们再谈
We'll talk later.
警卫会带你去房间
One of the guards will take you up to the residence.
比尔  什么事情
All right, Bill. what is it?
好消息
I have very good news.
杰克·鲍尔
Jack Bauer just
刚恢复了一个杜巴库隐藏的数据库
Recovered a database hidden on Dubaku.
政府里为他卖命的人的名单
It contains the names of everyone
都在里面
In the government who was working with him.
有多少人
How many?
接近百人
Close to a hundred people,
包括所有的单位
Across all agencies.
-其中一些还是位高权重的  -天哪
- Some at very high levels. - My god.
杜巴库保存了所有人的详细资料
Dubaku kept detailed files on every person.
这正是
This is exactly
我们想要的  总统阁下
What we've been working toward, Madam president.
阴谋
We can finally put an end
终于可以结束了
To this conspiracy.
我想你已经
I assume you've already
-针对这些情报展开行动了吧  -是的
- Begun acting on this information. - Yes.
事实上  拉里·莫斯刚刚又揪出来两个
As a matter of fact, Larry Moss just identified two more individuals
在联调局的内鬼  也在名单之上
Working within FBI who were on the list.
他确信联调局已经安全了
He's confident the Bureau is secure.
下一步怎么办
What's the next step?
我在跟联调局联手做一次内部大搜捕
I'm working with FBI to coordinate an interagency sweep.
一小时内  就可以开始抓人了
We should start making arrests within the hour.
比尔  我真不知道该说
Bill, I don't know what to say
什么感谢的话才好
To thank you.
你今天所做的一切
What you have done here today
我们会没齿难忘
Puts all of us in your debt.
谢谢夸奖  总统阁下
I appreciate that, Madam president,
但是我们还有许多人要感谢
But there are a lot of people to thank,
包括杰克·鲍尔
Including Jack Bauer.
他将会在明天早晨
He's scheduled to resume his testimony
参议院的听证会上出庭受审
Before the senate committee tomorrow morning.
这点我很清楚
I'm aware of that.
总统阁下  恕我冒昧
Madam president, forgive me
也许我说话有点过分
If I'm out of line, but I feel
但是我感觉  迈尔参议员
Senator mayer is on a personal crusade
有些针对杰克
Against Jack.
他已得偿所愿  也该得饶人处且饶人了
He's already taken his pound of flesh.
他解散了反恐组
He dismantled CTU,
毁掉了那些曾为这个国家
Attacked the reputations of people
鞠躬尽瘁的人们的名誉
Who've served this country with honor.
如今  他又想拿杰克来杀鸡儆猴
Now he wants to make an example of Jack.
这样做是不对的  总统阁下
It isn't right, Madam president,
尤其是看到今天杰克的表现
Especially after today.
你要我怎么做呢  比尔
What are you asking me to do, Bill?
我想让您跟迈尔参议员谈谈
I'm asking you to speak to senator mayer.
杰克·鲍尔帮我们拯救了这个国家
Jack Bauer helped save this country.
不该让他在监狱里度过余生
He doesn't deserve to spend the rest of his life in prison.
我很欣赏你的观点  比尔
I appreciate your sentiments, Bill,
但请容我再斟酌一下
But I'm going to have to think about this.
我已别无他求  总统阁下
That's all I'm  asking, Madam president.
谢谢您
Thank you.
你来这干嘛
What the hell are you doing here?
-我得跟你谈谈  -谈什么
- I need to talk with you. - About what?
我告诉过你  我在追踪一条线索
I told you I was going to follow up on a lead.
不  你说过这件事情一完
No, you said you were going to turn yourself in
-你就会投案自首  -我会的
- As soon as this was over. - And I will.
但是这事情还没完
But this ain't over yet.
还会有恐怖袭击
There's going to be another attack.
就在这里  在华盛顿
Here in D.C.
杜巴库已经被羁押  他已经供出了
Dubaku is in custody. he's already provided us
在政府里为他卖命的所有人的名单
With a list of everyone in the government that was working with him.
这次不是杜巴库
It's not Dubaku.
是他老板  朱玛
It's his boss, Juma.
他知道他即将失去对自己国家的控制权了
He knows he's about to lose control of his country.
所以他企图召集他手下的亡命徒
So he's going to try and rally his people behind him
-合力反击我国  -你是怎么知道的
- By striking back at the U.S. - How do you know this?
我追查到一个情报来源
I tracked down a source.
什么情报来源
What source?
我曾和他共同为爱默生团伙卖命
He was one of the men I worked with on emerson's crew.
他能跟在桑加拉的朱玛政权
He had a direct line of communication
进行直接联络
With the Juma regime in Sangala.
从他那得到情报不太容易
It wasn't easy getting the information out of him,
但我确信情报可靠
But I'm convinced it's accurate.
-那你应该向联调局报告  -不
- Then you should hand it over to FBI. - No.
情报来源表明
My source tells me
行动将会在晚上七点钟开始
That the window opens at 1900 hours.
等联调局办完那些
By the time the FBI
繁文缛节的官文程序
Wades through their procedures and red tape,
一切就太迟了
It's going to be too late.
袭击目标是什么
What's the target?
他不清楚具体的目标
He doesn't know the exact target,
但目标绝对是攻击价值高
But it's definitely going to be of high value
破坏后负面效应大的
And high impact.
他给了我一个名字
He gave me the name of somebody
-此人参与了行动计划  -谁
- Who's been involved in the planning. - Who?
莱恩·伯内特
Ryan Burnett.
迈尔参议员的办公室主任
Senator Mayer's chief of staff.
是的
That's right.
从一开始  他就参与其中
He's been involved from the very beginning.
迈尔呢
What about Mayer?
没
No.
他没参与
He's not involved.
你确定吗
You're sure about that?
确定
Yeah.
你最好是没跟我撒谎  托尼
You better not be lying to me, Tony.
千真万确  杰克
This is real, Jack.
伯内特会在杜巴库的名单上找到
Burnett will be on Dubaku's list.
只要他发现杜巴库被羁押
As soon as he finds out that Dubaku's in custody,
他会马上逃之夭夭  你没多少时间了
He'll start running. you don't have a lot of time.
我已经派人跟踪他了
I've already got a tail on him.
听着  杰克
Listen, Jack,
如果你相信我
If you're with me,
咱们第一大街跟宪法路的交汇口见
Meet me at the corner of First and Constitution.
我需要你助我一臂之力
I need your help.
让大家久等了
Thank you for your patience.
你们有些人一定已经知道
As I'm sure some of you already know,
我们的政府及其下属机构
Our government and its ancillary agencies,
包括咱们这
Including this office,
都被杜巴库
Have been infiltrated by operatives
安插了内鬼
In league with ike Dubaku.
请讲  参议员
Yes, senator?
莱恩  你能进来一下吗
Ryan, can you step in here?
好的  长官
Yes, sir.
我现在要去白宫
I'm going to the White House.
怎么了
Sir?
关于杰克·鲍尔的事情
President Taylor wants to speak to me
泰勒总统要跟我谈谈
Regarding Jack Bauer.
鲍尔
Bauer?
他怎么了
What about him?
我也不清楚
I don't know,
不过一会儿就知道了
But we'll find out soon enough.
太奇怪了
It's odd, though.
什么太奇怪了  长官
What is, sir?
今天早上  鲍尔就被联调局
Bauer was pulled away
从听证会上带走
From the senate hearings this morning
去帮他们调查一宗案子
To help the FBI with an investigation.
现在总统又要跟我谈
And now the president
关于他的事情
Wants to talk to me about him.
无巧不成书啊
I don't like the timing of this.
带上你的手提电脑  莱恩
Grab your laptop, Ryan.
你跟我一块儿去
I want you there with me.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
[人马就位  准备行动]
Units in place. Operation on schedule.